Daemun
Boys' High School is
where all the
troublemakers go to
In other words
it's a school for idiots
It's a a dog-eat-dog
world where
only strength matters
Hey!
Either sleep
in the morning
or get out and play
you b*******!
Shut up when
I'm taking a nap
There's an invisible
hierarchy here
[King, Bully
Average, Loser]
I'm…
Hong Il-tak
a second-year student
My position here is…
Stop it, that hurts
I'm at the bottom
[Loser]
Until middle school
I was the same
as Kim Hyeong-ju
My adorable doll, Il-tak
Hand
Want to know how I
ended up like this?
-V
-Fine
If only that d***
puberty kicked in
I have to escape
Hyeong-ju's bullying
Are you sensitive?
- Let's see!
- Stop it
Come on! Stop it!
Hey, I'm sorry
That's why I told
you to stop…
F***
Are you talking
back to me?
Stay still
Unless you want
a beating
That's enough